https://dupagepads.org/about/privacy-statement/

DuPage County HMIS Baseline Privacy Notice
When you visit our website at www.dupagepads.org, we want you to feel secure that we are respecting your privacy.
The only private information we have about you is the information you choose to give us (such as by providing feedback or completing a form or sending an email). We do not share your personal information with any third parties.
Privacy for Internet Users
If you are a visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes your Internet Service Provider’s domain name and aggregates information about which pages you visited. We use this information to improve the content of our web pages. We do not collect e-mail addresses, postal addresses or telephone numbers to contact visitors to our website.
We do not currently use “cookies” on our website, but may do so in the future for the purpose of serving you better. A “cookie” is a small element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Data collected from “cookies” helps us determine how many people visit certain pages, ultimately enabling us to improve our site design and content. Your web browser can be set to provide you a notice before accepting any “cookies”.
We are not responsible for the collection and use of information by companies or organizations outside of DuPagePads Inc. that may be linked to our website.
E-Mail
Generally, any e-mail that you send to us, and our responses, are not sent in a secure or encrypted manner.
Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of your children is essential. For that reason, our website is not structured to attract children under the age of 13. Parental consent is required for children under 13 to provide personally identifiable information via our website.
How to Contact Us
If you would like additional information, or if you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please fill out our online form.
Donor Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of our donors and appreciate their support. DuPagePads does not trade, rent or sell donor information to any other entity or organization. This policy applies to all information received by DuPagePads online, electronic, written or verbal.
Search
About DuPagePadsAbout DuPagePads
Community Impact
Annual Reports
DuPage Pads Staff
Board of Directors
Our History
Employment Opportunities
November 4th, 2020
Please join us virtually Wednesday, November 4th to share in an inspirational message and new client developments during the 18th Annual Wake Up Your Spirit Virtual Day, featuring Keynote Speaker, Angela Sanchez.
Learn More
Latest Tweets30 NovA $35 donation can empower children in our care with school supplies for virtual, in person, and hybrid education. Donate this #GivingTuesday and help supply more children with the tools they need for success in the upcoming school semester. Donate now at https://e.givesmart.com/events/jDx/ Reply on Twitter 1333485876823908353Retweet on Twitter 13334858768239083531Like on Twitter 13334858768239083533Twitter 133348587682390835328 OctThis chilly #WishlistWednesday we ask you to remember how a slight change in weather can affect those experiencing homelessness. Items like waterproof gloves and jackets make a world of difference to those we serve. Can you help by donating needed items? https://amzn.to/2JARG7x Reply on Twitter 1321498557287989249Retweet on Twitter 13214985572879892492Like on Twitter 13214985572879892494Twitter 1321498557287989249
Hosting Congregations
Church of the Holy Ghost – Wood Dale
Community Presbyterian Church – Clarendon Hills
Community United Methodist Church – Naperville
Congregation Etz Chaim – Lombard
Elmhurst Presbyterian Church
First Church of Lombard UCC
First Congregational Church of Glen Ellyn UCC
Gold – Innovator ETFs
Gold – Invesco Ltd.
Gold – Lift Works
Gold – Republic Bank
Gold – The Schulte Wealth Management Group
Gold – Tuk Tuk Naperville
Gold – West Suburban Bank
Gold – Wheaton Bank & Trust Company
Silver – Access Community Health Network
Silver – Busey Bank
Silver – Nicor Gas
Silver – Ostrander Construction Inc.
Silver – Retriever Merchant Solutions
Silver – Richards Graphic Communications
Silver – Sullivan Taylor, Gumina & Palmer
Silver – Viking Travel/ASTA
Silver – Villa Park Office Equipment, Inc.
Community Partnerships
360 Youth Services
Access DuPage
Bridge Communities
C.H.A.D.
Catholic Charities
Community Career Center, Inc.
Community Crisis Center, Inc.
DuPage Community Clinic
DuPage County Department of Probation
DuPage County Health Dept.
DuPage County Workforce Development
DuPage Housing Authority
DuPage Workforce Board
Family Shelter Service
Glen Ellyn Walk-In Ministry
Hamdard Center for Health and Human Services
Healthcare Alternatives Systems (H.A.S), Inc.
Healthcare for Homeless Veterans
HOPE Fair Housing
Hope’s Front Door
IDHS, Division of Rehabilitation Services
Literacy Volunteers of DuPage
Loaves and Fishes
Lombard & Villa Park Walk-In Ministry
Love Christian Clearing House
World Relief
Important information about our COVID-19 response.
During the pandemic, DuPagePads continues to follow best safety guidelines and provide Interim Housing
for persons experiencing homelessness through a combination of support services, hotel-based housing
and small-capacity congregate shelter. Housing evaluations for anyone without shelter are available
Monday – Friday from 8am – 12pm
via phone at 630-682-3846. Individuals and families
are asked contact the Client Service Center before seeking access at
Emergency Housing locations.
Interim Housing capacity is limited. DuPagePads makes every effort to help someone experiencing homelessness explore alternative housing options including provided Emergency Housing services.
If you see someone who is unsheltered please contact DuPagePads Street Outreach at 866.682.3846 x2275 with details. Thank you.
Read
More Here
